Mom, you came without telling me.
Flashback.
Who is it that sent you to your hometown?
Tell me, I sent you. It's been a
long time since you went to my house.
My mother wants to
see my father. If you send me for four days, I will
send you. Go home and work. Why are you
so angry? What did you say? Even if I told you, I
sent you.
But do one thing. Don't fight with your height and
slap me.
They will send you away. Again, I will
talk to the elders and tell them that some little child
did something wrong without knowing it and I will let him go
.  What if
you're the one who's still at home and not working
[music]?
After four days, you and the big guys
come and leave [laughter]
Please subscribe and follow,